https://www.ndchost.com/legal/privacy-statement/

Overview
Please take a moment to review our policy in detail. To assist you, we offer this short summary:
We use your personal information to fulfill your requests and serve you better We do not share your personal details with outside third parties without your consent.
We will only send you materials you have indicated you want to receive, and we will honor your opt-out requests.
We use cookies as part of our affilation program to indicated referers.
We adopt careful procedures to protect your data, and use special care to protect credit card and critical data.
We do reserve the right to use or disclose information in certain circumstances, such as to satisfy a legal request or protect our property.
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:
The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
The date and time you access our site;
The pages you visit; and if you linked to NDC Host from another website, the address of that website.
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors - to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors are using. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.
If You Send Us Personal Information
If you choose to provide us with personal information, as in an e-mail, by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our website, or other method, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us locate for you, the information you have requested. In the case of an order submission, that information is kept and held in a secure billing database for access by authorized personnel and is utilized for billing purposes which may include collection and the release of said information to approved collection facility or 3rd party collection company. Your information is not shared with any other parties other then Network Data Center Host and its subsidiary companies if required unless otherwise specified or required by law.
Employee/Representative Accountability
Only those Network Data Center Host representative that have a legitimate business purpose for accessing and handling personal information obtained by us are given authorization to do so. The unauthorized access or use of such information by a NDC representative is prohibited and constitutes grounds for disciplinary action with may escalate to termination.
Additionally, our information management systems are configured in such a way as to block or inhibit employees from accessing information that they have no authority to access (such as credit card information).
The Accountability of Network Data Center Hosts Business Partners
Our trusted vendors and business partners are responsible for processing or handling some of the information that we receive. These vendors and business partners are not authorized to use such information for purposes beyond those specified by us and are required to preserve the confidentiality with which we treat such information.
If you feel that Network Data Center Host, or any of our agents, representatives or employees, are violating this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail to privacy@ndchost.com or via the contact information available on our site www.ndchost.com.
Website Security
Areas requiring submission of valuable or critical information utilize 128bit SSL encryption when accessed via https://. Every effort is made from an administrative stand point to ensure the security of Network Data Center Host's websites and related content. Information presented on the NDC website is private information and may not be distributed or copied. The use of the name Network Data Center Host, NDC Host, cPlicensing, or other affiliated Network Data Center Host company names require express written permission by an authorized NDC agent. Please report any misuse of the name, logo, or associated text and documentation to our fraud department via e-mail to fraud@ndchost.com. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to access, change information, or otherwise cause damage.
Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used for no other purposes and are scheduled for regular destruction.
Unauthorized attempts to change information on this or any other Network Data Center Host media is strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986.
Use of cookies
A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a web site, is placed by the web server into the browser's application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the web site to "recognize" you as a unique individual.
Cookies are used to as a part of our affiliation program to log the referrer source, this is a numerical affiliation number is recorded and submitted to us via website submit forms, it's contents are for he sole use by NDC Host to credit those affiliates whom referred you to us.
Cookies can be removed from your hard drive. Also, depending on what type of web browser and what browser version you are using, you may be able to change the properties on your cookie file so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removing cookies. Affiliates and users beware, the removal of the cookie will discard the affiliate number and credit will not be given to the referring affiliate.
Links to Other Sites
Our website has links to private organizations, with their permission. Once you access another site through a link that we provide you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. Network Data Center Host is not responsible or liable for the independent privacy policies of these third-party sites. You should consult the privacy policies at those sites to determine how your information may be used. If you are unclear of areas of their policy, or in the event a privacy policy is not available on the third party site, contact them through other means to discuss your security concerns.
Notification of Changes
We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy before their effective date so you will always know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You are responsible for periodically checking our web site for changes to this Privacy Policy. Every effort is made to prevent retroactive modifications to this document though we reserve the right to do so, and such a change may maybe required by governmental or judicial measures.
Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or to "Opt-Out"
If you would like us to access, update, change, or delete information we have about you in our marketing database (subject to any applicable legal exceptions), would like to opt out of receiving further communications from contact us via e-mail to opt-out@ndchost.com, or if have questions about our privacy policy, please contact our Privacy Coordinator via e-mail to privacy@ndchost.com.
Revised: Wednesday, December 2nd, 2009
Services
Web Hosting
WordPress Hosting
Cloud Servers
Dedicated Servers
cPanel Licensing
Domain Registration
Network Data Center Host, Inc.
Toll Free: 1-888-294-8649International: 1-949-388-8169
Copyright © 2020
Privacy,
Terms,
AUP
We accept PayPal, Credit Card, Check, Wire Transfer, Bitcoin, and most other popular crypto coins
